answergrab.com 2013-08-15

# Privacy Policy | AnswerGrab.com

AnswerGrab (MMP) is very committed to protecting the privacy of our users. The goal of this policy is to outline the information that we may gather and how we use it. This policy pertains to [www.monstermarketplace.com ](http://www.monstermarketplace.com/). For further information, please also view our Malware Policy & Disclaimer

## Overview

  * MMP collects personal information and non-personal information when you register with www.monstermarketplace.com.
  * MMP does not lease, sell, or share your personal identifiable information (eg: full name or email address). This does not include trusted third parties who aid us.
  * We limit access to your personal information to employees who we believe need to come in contact with your information to better serve you. Employees may only access your data for permitted businesses functions.
  * MMP does have physical, procedural, and electronic safeguards put in place to protect you.
  * MMP may collect aggregate date about you and your store so to better serve you.
  * If you contact MMP, we may keep a record of that correspondence and we may collect your email address.
  * AnswerGrab may include content and ads from third parties that may perform user activity tracking other than that described herein.
  * MMP may need to disclose personal information when required by law.
  * MMP may use third party service providers to serve ads and emails on our behalf.
  * MMP is not intended for use by children under the age of 13.
  * Like most websites, MMP uses cookies to enhance the overall experience. You may set your browser to not accept cookies if you so desire. 

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

MMP may update this policy to reflect changing business practices. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement.
